{
    "subject": "resource/NetSuite",
    "predicate": "ontology/foundationPlace",
    "object": "resource/California",
    "human_readable": "NetSuite was founded in California.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9307095408439636,
            "question": "Was NetSuite established in a different state than California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9255354404449463,
            "question": "Is NetSuite headquartered in California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8916966915130615,
            "question": "Can we say that NetSuite's origin is linked to California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8884457349777222,
            "question": "Where was NetSuite founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6552914977073669,
            "question": "Can we assume NetSuite is a Californian company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6466694474220276,
            "question": "In which US state did NetSuite originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6117025017738342,
            "question": "What region is associated with the founding of NetSuite?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3876497745513916,
            "question": "What state is NetSuite from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22447507083415985,
            "question": "What type of company is NetSuite?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09442154318094254,
            "question": "Is California known for its technology companies?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=NetSuite was founded in California.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4483_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of company is NetSuite?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4483_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What state is NetSuite from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4483_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What region is associated with the founding of NetSuite?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4483_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4483_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4483_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4483_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4483_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4483_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4483_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4483_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4483_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4483_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4483_57.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that NetSuite was founded in California. The relevant text from the document is:\n\n\"NetSuite was founded in 1998 and is headquartered in San Mateo, California.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document states, \"NetSuite was founded in 1998 and is headquartered in San Mateo, California,\" which supports the statement that NetSuite was founded in California."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}